BUKOLA VICTOR David

23, Hospital Road, Wukari, Taraba State, Nigeria | 08166622909 | davidbukola1@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

A dedicated and adaptable web developer with a background in psychology and diverse professional experience. Skilled in front-end and back-end technologies including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Laravel, and Node.js. Known for integrity, creative problem-solving, and the ability to learn quickly and work effectively both independently and in teams.

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Front-End Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React)
- Back-End Development (PHP, Laravel, Node.js)
- Version Control (Git, GitHub)
- Responsive Design
- Team Collaboration
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Communication Skills
- Professionalism and Adaptability

EDUCATION

University of Ilorin, Kwara State

| Bachelor of Science (B.Sc. Hons), Psychology | 2016–2021 |
|---|-----------|
| Government Day Secondary School, Ilorin | 2007–2013 |
| Grace Foundation Nursery/Primary School, Ilorin | 2004-2007 |

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React
- PHP, Laravel, Node.js
- MySQL, MongoDB (Basic)
- Python (Basic scripting)
- Solidity (Beginner)
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Computer System Networking

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

2022-Present

Designed and deployed a responsive merchant e-commerce website in 2023 using HTML,
CSS, Javascript and NodeJS.

- Built dynamic user interfaces and integrated payment features for small businesses.
- Manage version control and deployments using Git and hosting platforms like cPanel.

| Century Interactive Company (Remote) | 2022-2023 |
|--|-----------|
| Position: Call Reviewer | |
| PortOne Technology Hub | 2022 |
| Position: Computer Instructor | |
| National Home Grown School Feeding Program | 2022 |
| Position: Enumerating Officer | |
| National Youth Service Corps | 2021–2022 |
| Position: Commerce Teacher (SS1 & SS2) | |
| Winners Golden Bet | 2016–2021 |
| Position: Manager | |
| Matrix Café | 2015–2016 |

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

Position: Café Attendant

- Deputy Clerk, Student Representative Council University of Ilorin (2019–2021)
- Principal Corp Member GDSS Wukari, Taraba State (NYSC, 2022)
- Financial Secretary Education CDS Group (NYSC, 2022)
- General Secretary Winners Corpers' Fellowship, Wukari (NYSC, 2022)

LANGUAGES

- English Professional
- Yoruba Native/Bilingual
- Hausa Basic

INTERESTS

A lifelong learner passionate about technology and web development. I enjoy exploring new tools, solving problems creatively and working with others to build impactful digital products. In my spare time, I read, write and explore new places to stay active.

REFEREES

Available upon request.